http://www.ringtonescompass.com/terms.asp

Top Ringtones Of The Week
Shawn MendesMercy - downloadAlessia CaraScars To Your Beautiful - downloadClean BanditRockabye (Feat. Sean Paul and Anne... - downloadPost MaloneCongratulations (Feat. Quavo) - downloadJames ArthurSay You Won't Let Go - downloadThe ChainsmokersCloser (Feat. Halsey) - downloadGucci ManeBoth (Feat. Drake) - downloadKygoIt Ain't Me (Feat. Selena Gomez) - download
Search Ringtones by Artists:
0..9
z
y
x
w
v
u
t
Search
Enter search keywords:
Popular Artists
Migos
Culture
download
The Chainsmokers
Memories...Do Not Open
download
Big Sean
I Decided
download
Bryson Tiller
True to Self
download
Terms & Privacy
At RingtonesCompass, your privacy is one of the most important issues to us! The following Privacy Policy looks over various aspects of the use of the personal information, which is being obtained from you. Specifically, what we do with it and what procedures do we take to protect it.
The Information That's Being Collected
The moment you register an account with RingtonesCompass, you generate a password-protected subscription that will give you the opportunity to order and download ringtones, graphics, games and additional items. Throughout this process you provide us with your personal details such as your name, a lawful email address, cellphone number and address, as well as detailed billing information, including credit card number and expiration date.
Once you begin to use your account, we keep track of your cooperation with us, such as your site activity, order and payment history, and all messages that you send us. You also have the ability to enter cellphone numbers of your friends and family in an occasion you want to send them text messages. The following numbers are used exclusively for that purpose.
Our servers collect and preserve technical information such as users' IP addresses browser types and operating systems. These details supply us with instruments that can help us analyze the way our website is used, and can also be gathered and shared with third parties such as advertisers.
Information Regarding Minors
The exploitation of RingtonesCompass is restricted to those over the age of 13. However, if you are between the age13 and 17, you must attain parental permission both to make the registration process complete and to be able to download content. We will not intentionally collect personal details from users under 13 years of age, and we obligate to delete immediately any information of that sort in case it will be brought to our attention.
Application of Information you Supply
RingtonesCompass.com uses the details that are being supplied to us for purposes firmly connected to the most proficient use of our site. We use it to authenticate users, to contact customers for billing and administration purposes, and for domestic examination and reporting.
It's possible that you'll be receiving from us certain site and service announcement updates via your email address or cell phone number, and inform you about exclusive deals and promotions obtainable through trusted partners. You have the chance to decline this option of receiving promotional messages, however, not service related messages, through a link in emails that are being sent to you.
Cookies
RingtonesCompass.com utilizes cookies (pieces of information received by your browser and stored on your computer) to follow how you found our website and your purchasing and searching actions. This enables us to reward our partners and further develop our services. Your payment data is not kept on cookies, nor is any other information of that sort.
Disclosure of Personal Information to Third Parties
RingtonesCompass will not sell, rent or share in any way your personal details with non-affiliated third parties, without your permission. Nevertheless, we do share your information with secure service providers, such as phone companies. This gives us an opportunity to guarantee proper billing for the services we offer. These service providers may not necessarily apply this data for any meaning other than providing those services for us.
We may disclose your data to third parties when we have a motive to believe that we are obligated to do so by law. Finally, we may relocate information, including any personally identifiable information, to a successor unit in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, sale of assets or other corporate change that concerns our website.
Third Party Sites
RingtonesCompass includes links to and advertisements for websites operated by third parties whose privacy policies may be different from ours. Even though we attempt to associate only with trustworthy sites, we cannot be held responsible for the information practices of these websites.
Protecting your information
RingtonesCompass makes sensible efforts to maintain your personal information but we cannot assure that communications between you and the website will be secure from illicit access by third parties. In the unlikely event of a security violation which results in the compromising of sensitive personal information, we will, without a doubt, alert you at once.
Referral Program
Any data collected through the Referral Program is used solely for the functioning of the Referral Program.
Contact Information
If you have any questions or suggestions concerning our Privacy Policy, you are welcome to contact us at info @ RingtonesCompass.com
Supported Carriers: AT&T Alltel Boost Mobile Cellular One Cingular Edge MetroPCS Nextel Rogers Sprint Suncom T-Mobile U.S. Cellular Verizon Bell Vodafone Orange O2 Virgin Mobile
Site Map | Ringtones | Wallpapers |
Contact Info | Help | Terms & Privacy | wap ringtones - wap downloading
